you recently with the shirt that says
2027, the year everything changed. So
what's happening?
>> I do believe that in a couple of years,
and this is not only Bashar's
prediction, it's a prediction from other
psychics as well that have tapped into
this. It does appear that in about 2027,
we will actually be introduced openly to
extraterrestrials. We will know they
exist. And so it's the changes that
happen from that point forward that
we're really talking about is now that
we know openly that such things are real
and such beings exist and that they're
going to interact more openly with our
society, what does that change in all of
the different, you know, categories of
human endeavor and how what do those
changes look like and how quickly do
they occur or how slowly do they occur
depending on what those human categories
are. So the idea may be that there will
be phases to this contact. Let's say for
example, they might suddenly just park
their ships out over the ocean or
something like that where we can see
them and they might stay there long
enough where we can get over our
excitement and our confusion and our
surprise at seeing them and get used to
the fact that the ships are there or
maybe a long period of time. that could
that could last months
>> and then maybe we start going, "Okay,
they're here." So, just the idea of
being able to calm down and settle down
by being exposed to a ship hovering over
the ocean in plain sight of hundreds of
thousands of people and nothing
happening gets us used to the fact that
someone is standing there waiting for us
to calm down and get used to their
presence. that can go a long way toward
then the next step being able to land
and stand and step out of the ship and
say, "Yeah, here we are." So, they could
do this in phases to get us used to the
idea that they're here. I'm not saying
that open contact would suddenly be a
major, you know, shock in the sense of,
oh yeah, now you just have to get used
to the fact that you're standing 2 ft
away from a Plleadian. No, they'll do it
in a way that allows us the opportunity
to absorb it at least to some degree
before they openly introduce themselves
because that wouldn't serve any purpose
for us to go into psychological panic
and then try to have contact. So they'll
ease us into it in some way, shape or
form. That's my like you know religion
and politics and economics and sociology
and psychology and and all of that. So,
uh, it's just that I think 2027 will be
the catalyst, the beginning of that
change because it'll be relatively
undeniable from that point forward that
ETSs do exist because they will be
openly introducing themselves to our
society. Um, you know, and so for some
people it'll be like a given. Yeah,
sure. We knew they were always there.
For some people it'll be surprise. So it
just depends on how quickly someone can
absorb all of the change that's going to
happen with that introduction. So but to
me that's that's kind of the beginning
of it. That's that's the starting point
of the change is 2027.
That's the reason why I want to do the
class is to provide more of this
information so that they have something
that they can grab on